{
  "cards": [
    {"question":"What company does Hoshimachi Suisei belong to?", "answer":"Hololive", "difficulty": "easy"},
    {"question":"When is Hoshimachi Suisei's birthday?", "answer":"March 22nd", "difficulty": "easy"},
    {"question":"How old is Hoshimachi Suisei?", "answer":"18.4 years old", "difficulty": "medium"},
    {"question":"When did Hoshimachi Suisei debut?", "answer":"March 22, 2018", "difficulty": "hard"},
    {"question":"When did Hoshimachi Suisei move to Hololive?", "answer":"December 1, 2019", "difficulty": "medium"},
    {"question":"When was Hoshimachi Suisei's Twitter and YouTube created?", "answer":"March 18, 2018", "difficulty": "hard"},
    {"question":"When did Hoshimachi Suisei first appear on THE FIRST TAKE?", "answer":"January 20, 2023", "difficulty": "medium"},
    {"question":"What was the first song Hoshimachi Suisei sang on THE FIRST TAKE?", "answer":"Stellar Stellar", "difficulty": "easy"},
    {"question":"What was the name of Hoshimachi Suisei's 2nd album?", "answer":"Specter", "difficulty": "easy"},
    {"question":"What is Hoshimachi Suisei's 5th original song?", "answer":"Now on Space", "difficulty": "hard"}
  ]
}